question_data = [
    { "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The song &quot;Megalovania&quot; by Toby Fox made its third appearence in the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, the clouds and bushes have the same artwork and are just different colors.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Deus Ex (2000) does not feature the World Trade Center because it was destroyed by terrorist attacks according to the game&#039;s plot.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: &quot;Justice rains from above!&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The game &quot;Pocket Morty&quot; has a Morty called &quot;Pocket Mortys Morty&quot;?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  &quot;the Zone&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Doki Doki Literature Club was developed in Japan.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Each piece in Tetris is called a tetris.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
